👪 Zayar Linn Naung

Q

JAVA DEVELOPER

- +959 984251436
- zayarlinnnaung.dev@gmail.com
- NorthOkkalapa, Yangon, Myanmar
- https://zayarlinnnaung-dev.netlify.app/



PROFILE



Hello I am Zayar Linn Naung and 23 years old. I am a TU student specialized in IT who passionate in web developing. I usually spend my leisure for programming. Most of my knowledge come from self-study. So I am also a fast learner who has strong passion to learn something new and powerful.

EXPERIENCE



May 2022 - Current

Java Developer

ACEPlus Solution Company Limited

Building (19), MICT Park, Hlaing Township Developing new modules and system maintenance for insurance systems used in FNI (First National Insurance), GGI (Grand Guardian Insurance), MI (Myanma Insurance), GWI (Global World Insurance), and so on.

May 2020 - July 2020

Manually Implementing Algorithm named DES in Java

Leading for creating encrypt/decrypt algorithm named DES without any frameworks or library for 6th BE thesis.

EDUCATION



2016 To Current

Bachelor of Engineering (IT)

Technological University (Hmawbi)

Hmawbi, Yangon

As being extremely passionate in IT, I joined TU specialized in IT. But unfortunately due to Covid and Military Coup,

I had to freeze my education since I was a 3rd year student.

2020 - 2021

Diploma in Ethical Hacking and Cyber Security

NCFE (UK)

Learnt a lot about web security, network and software security and so on.

SKILLS



HTML, CSS, JS Bootstrap

TypeScript

Angular

Spring

Spring Boot

JSF

Hibernate, JPA